(Leonard:)...so we came up with
kind of a cool solution.
Oh, yeah? What's that?
(Sheldon:)It's simple, really.
(Sheldon:)It occurred to me that
knowing and not knowing...
(Sheldon:)...can be achieved by creating a macroscopic
example of quantum superposition...
(Sheldon:)...the principle that a physical system exists
partially in all its possible states at once.
(Penny:)We were all thinking it, really.
(Penny:)It was kind of the elephant
in the room, so...
(Sheldon:)Anyway, um, I realized
if we each present you...
(Sheldon:)...with an account of
what your father wrote to you...
(Sheldon:)...only one of which is true,
and we don't tell you which one it is...
(Sheldon:)...you will forever be
in a state of epistemic ambivalence.
(Penny:)Yeah, and I said if it wasn't epistemic,
we might as well not do it.
(Bernadette:)Sit down, honey.
- Raj, you're up.
- Okay, um, ahem.